thebroth.com 2007-07-17

# Privacy Policy - TheBroth.com

_TheBroth.com ("TheBroth") takes your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it._

## 1\. What information does TheBroth collect?

TheBroth collects only the information required to provide you with access to services offered by TheBroth. Participating as an anonymous player in any of TheBroth's rooms does not require you to provide TheBroth with any personal information. Visitors to TheBroth who wish to sign up as a member of TheBroth need only provide TheBroth with a contact email address. 

## 2\. What is TheBroth's practice regarding cookies?

Cookies stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to TheBroth. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit TheBroth, although viewing or participating in any of TheBroth rooms requires cookies. Cookies alone do not give us any personally identifiable information about you. By adjusting your browser settings, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected. 

We also automatically receive and record information from our servers and from your browser, including your IP address, the time of your visit to pages on TheBroth, and information about the pages you visited. This information we gather through the use of tracking technologies cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you. 

We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: 

  1. Keeping count of return visits to our site;
  2. Accumulating and reporting anonymous statistical information on web site and advertisement usage;
  3. Keeping track of registered users' preferred settings. 

TheBroth allows other companies to display advertisements on our site, and these ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads placed by third parties are collected by TheBroth advertisers or their affiliates, and TheBroth does not have access to or control over this information. Unless you visit the web site of these companies and provide them with personally identifiable information about yourself, these tracking technologies tell those advertisers nothing about who you are. Our advertisers' use of tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies. 

## 3\. How does TheBroth use the information?

We use the information we gather for three general purposes:

  1. To determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to improve TheBroth's services;
  2. To fulfill your requests for certain services, such as allowing you to create personalized TheBroth rooms;
  3. To send you information regarding changes to TheBroth's services. 

## 4\. Does TheBroth share the information?

TheBroth will not share your personally identifiable information with other companies or people. 

TheBroth may share personally identifiable information if and when we are required to do so by law, such as in the case of responding to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process. 

## 5\. Privacy practices relating to registered members and their profiles

### 5a. Publishing information

As a registered member, you have the option (but not the obligation) to customize your forum profile, post in the forum, write in user blogs, comment on artworks and blog entries, and you're encouraged not to share personally identifiable information when doing so. Please review our safety tips and guidelines. 

### 5b. Contests and member reward schemes

If you opt to enter an art competition and you win and wish to claim your prize, or if you are eligible for a product in context of a member rewards scheme, you may be required to disclose your name and mailing address. For this purpose, TheBroth offers a secure server address form to ensure the security of your personal information. After your item has been shipped, TheBroth will permanently delete your address from TheBroth servers. Claiming any prize or reward and disclosing your address is completely optional. Please refer to our Terms of Service for the rules governing contests. 

### 5c. Online indicators and public profile information

As a member, when you are online at TheBroth, every visitor to TheBroth can see whether you're online by means of a flashing online indicator icon displayed behind your username. Every visitor to TheBroth can also view your profile and view information about your user history, including the date when you joined, how often you visited, to how many and which snapshots you have contributed, and how many and which snapshots you have submitted to the public gallery. Based on the tags that other users or yourself are adding to your artworks, a certain "style" may be displayed on your profile, indicating the tags that your artworks are most frequently associated with. Every visitor to TheBroth will be able to read your forum posts, blog entries and comments on blog entries and artworks. Every visitor to TheBroth will also be able to see in which mosaic room you were last and the date or time of that visit. You have the option to only visit your own hidden room, in which case the "last mosaic room" information will be hidden from all other users on TheBroth. 

### 5d. Friends list

You are able to accept, ignore or reject friend requests, and you can remove other users from your friends list at any time. Members of TheBroth that you accept as friends will be able to view the last page you have viewed and the time associated with the last page view. 

### 5e. Chat

Members at TheBroth can communicate in mosaic rooms via a chat system. All chat messages are being logged. We do not monitor the chat but we reserve the right to look up previous chat conversations in the context of dispute resolution. We will not disclose any information in the chat log other than if required to do so by law, such as in the case of responding to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process. 

## 6\. What are my options

Users who would rather not provide the data requested by our registration process (ie. a valid email address and password) do not need to register with TheBroth. You can still participate anonymously in TheBroth experience without registering. 

## 7\. How can I review and update my personally identifiable information?

TheBroth does not store personally identifiable information other than your email address. You can [unregister](http://www.thebroth.com/unregister.html) which will delete your account, and it will remove your name from gallery comments you may have made and from artworks you may have contributed to. Your posts in the forum will remain visible and continue to display your username. If you are experiencing problems with our services or you have questions about how our services work, you can contact us via our contact page. 

## 8\. How is my information secured?

TheBroth has security measures in place, such as routine backups and administrator-only server access, in order to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under our control. 

_Last updated: Oct 13, 2006_
